’87 was heaven…
Cruise is a romance film directed by Robert D. Siegel.
Set in the 1980s, a young Italian-American from the wrong side of
the tracks falls for a Jewish girl from Long Island.
Gio Marchetti, played by Spencer Boldman.
Jessica Weintraub, played by Emily Ratajkowski.
Anthony Panagopoulos, played by Noah Robbins.
Mama Fortunato, played by Kathrine Narducci.
Papa Fortunato, played by Gino Cafarelli.
Dinardo, played by Sebastian Maniscalco.
Cruise is an American romantic comedy film, written and directed by Robert D.
It stars Spencer Boldman, Emily Ratajkowski, Lucas Salvagno, Noah Robbins,
Gino Cafarelli, Kathrine Narducci and Sebastian Maniscalco.
Filmed in 2015, it was eventually released direct-to-video in
September 2018, by Vertical Entertainment.
The film explores themes of italian american, long island, new
york, love, wrong side of the tracks, jewish girl.
The tone is emotional.